<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Episodes on Nevada City News</title><link>https://nevadacity.news/episodes/</link><description>Recent content in Episodes on Nevada City News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nevadacity.news/episodes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Orange Fever: Dispatches from the Front Lines of Northern California's Pumpkin Uprising</title><link>https://nevadacity.news/2024/orange-fever-dispatches-from-the-front-lines-of-northern-californias-pumpkin-uprising/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nevadacity.news/2024/orange-fever-dispatches-from-the-front-lines-of-northern-californias-pumpkin-uprising/</guid><description>Your browser does not support the audio element. As the crisp tendrils of autumn begin to strangle the last gasps of summer, the denizens of Nevada City and its surrounding territories find themselves caught in the grip of a peculiar madness. The pumpkin fever descends, seizing the populace with an uncontrollable urge to partake in the bizarre ritual of gourd selection.
In this twisted landscape of agricultural torment, three infamous patches have risen to prominence, each offering its own unique brand of orange-tinted insanity.</description></item><item><title>Gold Rush to Madness: Nevada City's Twisted Tale of Progress and Preservation</title><link>https://nevadacity.news/2024/gold-rush-to-madness-nevada-citys-twisted-tale-of-progress-and-preservation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nevadacity.news/2024/gold-rush-to-madness-nevada-citys-twisted-tale-of-progress-and-preservation/</guid><description>Your browser does not support the audio element. OCTOBER 10, 2024 — Hold onto your hats, you savage beasts of the Sierra foothills, for Nevada City is on a wild ride through the treacherous gorge of progress, with one wheel teetering off the cliff of history and the other spinning furiously into the abyss of modernity. It&amp;rsquo;s a goddamn spectacle, I tell you, a high-wire act of civic acrobatics that would make even the most jaded politician&amp;rsquo;s eyes bulge with a mixture of fear and admiration.</description></item></channel></rss>